Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXIX is arranged in 19 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXX is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXXI is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXIX. 1935 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 424-0. 1935 Convention
    - General, 1934-1935 (Box 584, Folder 18)
    - General, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 424-1. 1935 Convention
    - Convention City, 1931-1935 (Box 584, Folder 20)
    - Convention City, 1930 (Box 584, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 424-2. 1935 Convention
    - Pullman Rates, 1931-1936 (Box 584, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 424-3. 1935 Convention
    - Badges, 1932-1935 (Box 584, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 424-4. 1935 Convention
    - Sweepstakes, 1932-1935 (Box 584, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 424-5. 1935 Convention
    - Convention Committee, 1932-1935 (Box 584, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 424-6. 1935 Convention
    - Hotels, 1933-1935 (Box 584, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 424-7. 1935 Convention
    - Non-Delegates, 1933-1935 (Box 584, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 424-8. 1935 Convention
    - Law Committee, 1934-1937 (Box 584, Folder 28)
    - Law Committee, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 424-9. 1935 Convention
    - Convention Call, 1934-1935 (Box 584, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 424-10. 1935 Convention
    - Delegates and Alternates, 1934-1936 (Box 584, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 424-11. 1935 Convention
    - Proposed Amendments to Laws, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 424-12. 1935 Convention
    - Convention Book, 1934-1935 (Box 584, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 424-13. 1935 Convention
    - Resolutions, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 424-14. 1935 Convention
    - Transportation for Delegates, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 424-15. 1935 Convention
    - Mileage and Per Diem Committee, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 424-18. 1935 Convention
    - Grand Lodge Officers' Reports, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 424-17. 1935 Convention
    - Requests for Committee Appointments. Delegates, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 424-20. 1935 Convention
    - Visitors' Attendance Cards, 1935 (Box 584, Folder 39)
- Series LXXX. FIVE-DAY WEEK
  - Sub-Series 426-0. Five-Day Week
    - General, 1930-1949 (Box 584, Folder 40)
    - General. Memorandum "The Five-Day Week in Industry" Compiled by Industrial Relations Section, Princeton University, 1930 (Box 584, Folder 41)
- Series LXXXI. UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE
  - Sub-Series 428-0. Unemployment Insurance
    - General, 1932-1935 (Box 584, Folder 42)
    - General, 1931 (Box 584, Folder 43)
    - General, 1930 (Box 584, Folder 44)